http://paperbagpb.tripod.com/privacy.html

paperbag
playback is now OUT OF THE BOX THEATRE!
HOME | ABOUT US | PLAYBACK | PERFORMANCES | SERVICES | PLAYERS | GALLERY | LINKS | CONTACT
Privacy Statement
PaperBag PlayBack Theatre Privacy Statement
PaperBag PlayBack Theatre has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to the privacy
of our subscribers, visitors, clients and audience members. Our website contains links to
other sites. PaperBag PlayBack Theatre is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.
Personal Information PaperBag PlayBack collects
personal information from its website, over the phone, in person or by other means of electronic correspondence such as email
or fax to undertake our daily artistic and administrative operations. Personal information includes information and opinions
that can identify an individual. Use of Personal Information PaperBag PlayBack will only use the personal information you have chosen to provide us for the purpose for
which it was collected, or a purpose related to the primary purpose for which you would reasonably expect it to be used.  PaperBag
PlayBack will not use it for any other purpose without your consent. No Sale of
Personal Information Under no circumstances will PaperBag PlayBack sell or receive
payment for licensing or disclosing your personal information. Enquiry forms
Our website uses enquiry forms for visitors to request information, products, and services. We
collect visitors’ contact information (like their email address). Contact information from the enquiry form is used
to send information to our enquirers. All information provided remains confidential. Email
Newsletter PaperBag PlayBack may provide newsletters and news updates containing information
about performances, products, and services. To enable this we collect contact information (like email addresses) from audience
members and website visitors. Contact information for the newsletter is used only for the delivery of the newsletter and news
updates. Subscribers may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Access and Correction: Personal Information If PaperBag PlayBack
holds your personal information we will where possible provide you with access to the information. PaperBag PlayBack will
take reasonable steps to correct the information so that it is accurate, complete and up to date. Use of Anonymous Information To monitor the use of its website PaperBag Playback
automatically gathers anonymous information like the numbers and frequency of visitors to the site. We only use such data
in the aggregate.  PaperBag Playback may publish or provide this aggregate data to other people. Audience Feedback PaperBag PlayBack also collects anonymous information
when audience members are invited to respond to surveys or offer written comments and testimonials about performances. The
surveys may ask for demographic information such as age, gender and postcode. This information is collected for research purposes,
is used in the aggregate (where possible), and remains anonymous.  PaperBag PlayBack may anonymously publish audience
comments and testimonials collected at its performances. Client Feedback
PaperBag PlayBack invites its clients to provide formal feedback through post-performance evaluation
questionnaires. This information is collected for the purposes of continuous improvement and is used in the aggregate (where
possible).   PaperBag PlayBack may publish credited client comments and testimonials but will do so only with your consent.
Choice/Opt-Out Our newsletter and news updates provide
subscribers with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us. Receipt of our service(s) may also be stopped
by contacting PaperBag PlayBack Theatre by post: 6 Darghan Street Glebe  NSW  2037, email: paperbagpb@hotmail.com,
or phone 0414 294 047. Disclosure There will
be occasions where it will be necessary for the PaperBag PlayBack  to disclose your personal information to third parties.
PaperBag PlayBack may be required by law to disclose the information, or PaperBag PlayBack may be required to disclose your
personal information to third parties to provide the service you have requested. However, the disclosure will only be made
where it is necessary to fulfil the purpose for which you disclosed your personal information. Otherwise than stated above,
we do not disclose personal information that you may give us, such as your name, address, email address or telephone number,
to any organisation or person outside PaperBag PlayBack unless you have authorised us to do so. Contacting the Web Site If you have any questions about this privacy statement,
the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:  PaperBag PlayBack Theatre by post:
6 Darghan Street Glebe  NSW  2037, email: paperbagpb@hotmail.com, or phone 0414 294 047.
